A Guide to the Adèle Goodman Clark papers, 1849-1978
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series II: Business/Civic Organization Correspondence, undated, 1903-1971
  - Subseries A: Adèle Clark, undated, 1908-1971
    - Campaign Committee Against the Equal Rights Amendment, 1938 (Box 29)
    - Chamberlayne Avenue Group, undated (Box 29)
    - Chamberlain, Thomas B., 1929 (Box 29)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle Civic League, undated (Box 29)
    - Children's Home Society of Virginia, 1930 (Box 29)
    - Cincinnati Museum of Art, 1948 (Box 29)
    - Citizens' Committee on the Status of Women in Virginia, 1967 (Box 29)
    - Citizens' Service Exchange, 1935 (Box 29)
    - City Planning Commission, undated, 1933-1937 (Box 29)
    - City-Wide Market Committee, 1940 (Box 29)
    - Civil Service Commission, U.S., 1931 (Box 29)
    - Commonwealth Club, 1966 (Box 29)
    - Commission of Inquiry on Public Service Personnel, 1935 (Box 29)
    - Communist Party of Richmond, 1956 (Box 29)
    - Community Life Campaign, 1922 (Box 29)
    - Community Recreation Association, 1934, 1937 (Box 29)
    - Congress of Racial Equity (CORE), 1956-1958 (Box 29)
    - Consultation and Evaluation Clinic, 1959 (Box 29)
    - Consumers' Boycott Against Japanese Aggression in China, undated (Box 29)
    - Co-operative Education Association of Virginia, 1924-1925, 1929 (Box 29)
    - Council of Jewish Juniors, 1931 (Box 29)
    - Crittenton [Florence] Mission, 1933-1935 (Box 29)
    - Cruelty to Animals, undated (Box 29)
    - Cultural Relations with Latin America-Committee, 1935 (Box 29)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution of Virginia, undated (Box 29)
    - Daughters of the King of Virginia, 1930 (Box 29)
    - Delver Woman's Club, 1947 (Box 29)
    - Democratic National Campaign Committee, 1932 (Box 29)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1923, 1951 (Box 29)
    - Democratic State Central Committee, 1932, 1935 (Box 29)
    - Democratic Woman's Club of Richmond, 1966 (Box 29)
    - Dietz Press, Inc., 1948 (Box 29)
    - Eastern State Hospital, undated, 1957-1965 (Box 30)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Evening School of Business Administration, University of Richmond, undated (Box 30)
    - Every Monday Club, 1931-1932 (Box 30)
    - Fair Employment Practice Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 30)
    - Family Planning Association of Northern Virginia, undated (Box 30)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1947 (Box 30)
    - Florance, Garden and Brown, 1959 (Box 30)
    - Food and Drug Administration, U.S., 1917 (Box 30)
    - Foreign Language Information Service, 1924 (Box 30)
    - Foreign Relations, Council on, 1933 (Box 30)
    - "The Forest" Memorial Association, undated (Box 30)
    - Fredericksburg Chamber of Commerce, 1928 (Box 30)
    - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, 1957 (Box 30)
    - Friends House, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Gary, Vaughn J., 1965 (Box 30)
    - General Education Board, 1931 (Box 30)
    - General Welfare Tax League, 1933 (Box 30)
    - Ginter Park Traffic Improvement Association, 1950-1959 (Box 30)
    - Ginter Park Women's Club, 1913 (Box 30)
    - Girl Scouts of Richmond, 1933-1934 (Box 30)
    - Glasgow House Discussion Group [School Desegregation], 1955 (Box 30)
    - Glass, [Senator] Carter, 1924, 1931 (Box 30)
    - Governor's Office--Commonwealth of Virginia, 1922-1956 (Box 30)
    - Graduate Nurses Association of Virginia, 1928 (Box 30)
    - Hampton Institute, 1928-1934 (Box 30)
    - Hanover Woman's Club, 1933 (Box 30)
    - Harrison and Bates, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Highland Springs Woman's Club, 1939 (Box 30)
    - Hollins College, 1916-1944 (Box 30)
    - Hopper, Claude W., 1927 (Box 30)
    - House of Delegates--Commonwealth of Virginia, 1928-1966 (Box 30)
    - Ideal Publishing Corporation, 1948 (Box 30)
    - I.J. Smith and Company, undated (Box 30)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1941 (Box 30)
    - International Correspondence Schools, 1906 (Box 30)
    - International Association of Machinists, 1954 (Box 30)
    - International Foundation, 1922 (Box 30)
    - Inter-Organizational Committee on the Status of Women in Virginia, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Jefferson Society, 1924-1929 (Box 30)
    - Jones and Robins, 1934 (Box 30)
    - Justice, Department of, 1950-1951 (Box 30)
    - Keller, Helen, 1951 (Box 30)
    - Kirsh and Bazile, 1935 (Box 30)
    - Labor's Committee for Civilian Relief in China, 1938 (Box 30)
    - League for the Promotion of Public School Education in Virginia, 1930 (Box 30)
    - League of Nations Association, 1923-1942 (Box 30)
    - Lindsay, H. David (Box 30)
    - Literary Digest, 1929 (Box 30)
    - Little Theatre League, 1920 (Box 30)
    - McGuire, Riely, Bryan and Eggleston, 1919 (Box 31)
    - Macmillan Company, undated, 1921 (Box 31)
    - Mapp, G. Walter, 1924,1929 (Box 31)
    - Marcuse, Mrs. Milton E., 1924 (Box 31)
    - Marlowe Tire Company, undated (Box 31)
    - Medical College of Virginia, 1928-1935 (Box 31)
    - Memorial Home for Girls--Highland Park, undated (Box 31)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1908-1932 (Box 31)
    - Miller for Governor Campaign, 1949 (Box 31)
    - Mission Helpers of Alabama, undated (Box 31)
    - Montague, Hill, 1929-1935 (Box 31)
    - Motion Picture Welfare League, 1916 (Box 31)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1920, 1955 (Box 31)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1927, 1945 (Box 31)
    - National Bridge Association, 1933 (Box 31)
    - National Civic Federation, 1922 (Box 31)
    - National Civil Service Reform League, 1927 (Box 31)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1931 (Box 31)
    - National Committee on Morale, 1941 (Box 31)
    - National Conference on Planning, 1936 (Box 31)
    - National Consumers' League, 1934-1937 (Box 31)
    - National Council of Women, undated (Box 31)
    - National Council of Negro Women, 1956 (Box 31)
    - National Economic League, 1929-1931 (Box 31)
    - National Emergency Council, 1934 (Box 31)
    - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1926-1933 (Box 31)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1955 (Box 31)
    - National Probation Association, 1931 (Box 31)
    - National Progressive League for Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1932 (Box 31)
    - National Public Housing Conference, 1937 (Box 31)
    - National War Savings Committee for Richmond, 1917 (Box 31)
    - National Woman's Party [includes recollection of Adèle Clark 1971], 1922 (Box 31)
    - National Women's Trade Union League of America--Life and Labor Bulletins, 1946-1948 (Box 31)
    - New Amsterdam Casualty Company, 1925 (Box 31)
    - Nicholson Street Civic Association, 1968 (Box 31)
    - Northside Neighborhood Council, 1939 (Box 31)
    - Old Richmond News, 1949 (Box 31)
    - Peace House, 1929 (Box 31)
    - People's Lobby, 1929-1931 (Box 31)
    - Pictorial Review Company, undated, 1924 (Box 31)
    - Poetry Society of Virginia, 1925 (Box 31)
    - Postmaster [John J. Mizelle], undated (Box 31)
    - Prison Association of New York, 1920 (Box 31)
    - Progressive Democrats, 1946 (Box 31)
    - Prohibition and Evangelical Association, 1916 (Box 31)
    - Prosperity Club, undated (Box 31)
    - Radcliffe College, 1943-1959 (Box 31)
    - Randolph Macon College, 1954, 1962 (Box 31)
    - Randolph Macon Woman's College Alumnae Association, 1946 (Box 31)
    - R.B. Chaffin and Company, 1909 (Box 31)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1933 (Box 31)
    - Retreat for the Sick Hospital, 1926 (Box 31)
    - Rice, Guy, 1929 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Area Committee for Public Schools, 1954 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Area Community Chest, 1956 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Area Tuberculosis Association, 1966 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Area University Center, Inc., 1950 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Artists Association, Inc., 1969 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Branch Foreign Policy Association, 1928 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Business and Professional Women's Club, 1927-1928 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Chamber of Commerce, 1925-1931 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Child Labor Committee, 1947 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Citizens Association, Inc., undated (Box 31)
    - Richmond Citizens Association, Inc., 1947 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Civic Association, undated (Box 31)
    - Richmond [City of] (Box 31)
      - Recreation Division/Recreation and Parks Department, 1942-1971 (Box 31)
      - Safety Director's Committee on Crime, undated (Box 31)
      - Regarding tax payments, 1965-1966 (Box 31)
    - Richmond, Civilian Defense Office, 1942 (Box 31)
    - Richmond Committee for Civil Rights, 1948 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Community Fund, 1926-1935 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Council for Peace Education, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Council of Social Agencies, 1929-1935 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Council on Adult Education, 1934-1944 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Council--Boy Scouts of America, 1915 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Dietary Food Center, undated (Box 32)
    - Richmond Education Association, 1927 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Female Institute--Alumnae [Woman's College of Richmond], 1932 (Box 32)
    - Richmond First Club, 1932 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Forward, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Inter-Club Council, 1930 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Jewish Community Center, 1965-1966 (Box 32)
    - Richmond News-Leader, 1928, 1955, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Professional Institute, 1956-1966 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Public Forum, 1951-1953 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Public Schools, 1917-1947 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Quartermaster Depot, 1943 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Times-Dispatch, undated, 1947, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Training School for Kindergartners, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Richmond Tuberculosis Association, 1931-1944 (Box 32)
    - Riley, Dr. Charles R., 1971 (Box 32)
    - Roosevelt Business and Professional League, Inc., 1932 (Box 32)
    - Rosenwald [Julius] Fund, 1929 (Box 32)
    - St. Luke's Hospital-McGuire Clinic, 1929 (Box 32)
    - St. Mary's Hospital Auxiliary, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Safeguarding the Moral and Spiritual Forces of the State, Committee for, 1917 (Box 32)
    - Satterfield, David [Congressman], 1970 (Box 32)
    - Savoy Hotel--London, undated (Box 32)
    - Seamen's Church Institute of America, 1928 (Box 32)
    - Sheltering Arms Hospital, 1951 (Box 32)
    - Sherwin, Miss Belle, 1926-1938 (Box 32)
    - Sigma Delta, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Social Science Research Council--Committee on Public Administration
      - "Administrative Redistricting in Germany Since 1918" Report, 1935 (Box 32)
      - Annual Reports, 1936-1937, 1939-1940, 1942-1943 (Box 32)
      - Annual Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 32)
      - "City Manager Government in Austin, Texas" Report, 1937 (Box 32)
    - Social Science Research Council--Committee on Public Administration (Box 33)
      - Committee Reports, Studies, Minutes of Meetings, 1935-1938 (Box 33)
      - Committee Reports, Studies, Outlines, Statement of Goals and Objectives, undated (Box 33)
      - Correspondence, 1935-1938 (Box 33)
      - "Sources of Information Concerning the Eighteenth Amendment" Report, 1928 (Box 33)
    - Social Security Administration, 1951 (Box 33)
    - South Carolina, University of, 1966-1967 (Box 33)
    - Southern Aid Society of Virginia, Inc., 1930 (Box 33)
    - Southern Conference for Human Welfare, undated, 1942 (Box 34)
    - Southern Conference for Human Welfare--Committee for Virginia, 1946-1947 (Box 34)
    - Southern Council on Women and Children in Industry, 1930 (Box 34)
    - Southern Dairies, Inc., 1935 (Box 34)
    - Southern Regional Committee of CPU, 1953 (Box 34)
    - Southern Regional Council, 1954-1955 (Box 34)
    - Southern School for Workers, 1946-1950 (Box 34)
    - Southern Woman's Educational Alliance, 1928-1932 (Box 34)
    - Southwest Virginia Museum, 1949 (Box 34)
    - Speed, Mrs. E.W., 1931 (Box 34)
    - State Commission on Conservation Development, 1929 (Box 34)
    - State Planters Bank and Trust Company, undated, 1938 (Box 34)
    - State Teachers College, 1924-1936 (Box 34)
    - Suffrage Archives Committee, 1952-1959 (Box 34)
    - Sullivan, Mrs. Frances, 1929 (Box 34)
    - Swannanoa Foundation, Inc., undated, 1940 (Box 34)
    - Swiss National Exhibition of Feminine Activities, 1928 (Box 34)
    - Tabb, John B. Memorial Association, 1922, 1933 (Box 34)
    - Times Democrat [New Orleans, LA], undated (Box 34)
    - Travelers (Tabb, Brocken, Braugh and Ragland), 1942, 1946 (Box 34)
    - Union for Democratic Action, undated (Box 34)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1922 (Box 34)
    - United World Federalists of VA, 1947 (Box 34)
    - Valentine Museum, 1931-1943 (Box 34)
    - Van Wormer Tree Service, Inc., 1966 (Box 34)
    - Vindicator Publishing Company, 1912 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Anti-Saloon League, 1922 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Association for Mental Health, 1955 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Association of Workers for the Blind, Inc.--Richmond Chapter, 1921-1925 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Capital Bicentennial Commission, 1937 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1925-1929 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Child Labor Committee, 1947 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Church Conference on Race Relations, 1930 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Commission on County Government, 1931 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Committee for Public Schools, undated (Box 34)
    - Virginia Committee to Save the Martinsville Seven, undated (Box 34)
    - Virginia Conference of Social Work, 1936-1956 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, undated (Box 34)
    - Virginia Consumers' League, 1938 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Council of Administrative Women in Education, 1929 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, 1949-1950 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Council on Human Relations, 1955-1957 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Council on Religious Education--Special Education and Financial Effort, 1931, 1936 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Council on State Legislation, 1947-1967 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Division of Motor Vehicles [State Highway Commissioners], 1933-1934 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Education Association, 1954-1955 (Box 34)
    - Virginia Federalist, 1947 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs, undated, 1929-1955 (Box 35)
    - Virginia History and Factbook Commission, undated (Box 35)
    - Virginia Interracial Commission/Committee, 1923-1945 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Junior Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 35)
    - Virginia League for Planned Parenthood, 1946 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1928 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1953-1956 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute--Cooperative Education Work in Agriculture and Home Economics, 1917, 1931 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Real Estate Association, 1921 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Social Science Association, 1929 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Society for Crippled Children and Handicapped Adults, 1944-1946 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Society for Crippled Children and Physically Handicapped Adults, 1947-1956 (Box 35)
      - Open Door News Bulletin, 1946-1955 (Box 35)
      - Easter Seal Society Bulletins, 1950-1957 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Society for Human Life, 1965-1970 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Society for Preservation of Public Schools, 1956 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Board of Education, 1931 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Board of Health, 1924 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, undated, 1935 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Commission on Conservation and Development, 1929 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Committees of One Hundred, 1944 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Library, 1931 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Library for the Blind and Physically Handicapped, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Virginia State Teachers Association [Colored], 1927 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Transit Company, 1948 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Tuberculosis Association, 1955 (Box 35)
    - Virginia Union University, 1930 (Box 35)
    - Virginia, University of, 1954, 1967 (Box 35)
      - Co-Ordinate College League, 1917-1918 (Box 35)
      - Institute of Public Affairs Extensions Division, 1923-1934 (Box 35)
    - Virginia, University of (Box 36)
      - Publications (Box 36)
        - Alumni Bulletins/News, 1921-1929 (Box 36)
        - Extension News, 1927-1928 (Box 36)
        - Newsletters, 1929-1965 (Box 36)
      - Record Extension Series, 1920-1928 (Box 36)
      - Summer Quarter Bulletins, 1928-1936 (Box 36)
    - Virginia Welfare Council, 1938 (Box 36)
    - Virginia Women's Christian Temperance Union, 1923-1924 (Box 36)
    - Virginia Women's Council of Legislative Chairman of State Organizations, 1924-1956 (Box 36)
    - Virginia Youth Movement for Social Betterment, 1935 (Box 36)
    - Washington [George] Bicentennial Commission, 1932 (Box 36)
    - Wheeler Defense Committee, 1925 (Box 36)
    - White Top Folk Festival, 1935 (Box 36)
    - Whitmell Farm Life School Junior League, 1922-1923 (Box 36)
    - Who's Who in Government, 1930 (Box 36)
    - Who's Who in Virginia, 1941 (Box 36)
    - William and Mary, College of, 1926-1948 (Box 36)
    - William and Mary, College of--Richmond Extension Division, 1929-1933 (Box 36)
    - Wilson [Woodrow] Foundation (Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1921-1927 (Box 37)
      - Newsletters and Miscellaneous Publications, 1921-1926 (Box 37)
    - Wilson [Woodrow] Institute of the Philippines, 1931 (Box 37)
    - Wilson [Woodrow] Memorial Society, 1929 (Box 37)
    - Woman's Auxiliary to the Medical Society of Virginia, 1952 (Box 37)
    - Woman's Centennial Congress, 1940 (Box 37)
    - Woman's Club, 1924, 1933, 1946 (Box 37)
    - Woman's Organization for National Prohibition Reform, undated (Box 37)
    - Woman's Who's Who, 1941 (Box 37)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1966 (Box 37)
    - Woody [Stuart] Defense Committee, 1951 (Box 37)
    - Wormeley, Carter [Bishop], undated, 1924-1934 (Box 37)
    - Young Democratic Clubs of Virginia, 1946 (Box 37)
    - Young Women's Christian Association, 1925-1959 (Box 37)
  - Subseries B: Edith Clark Cowles, undated, 1903-1939
    - Emmanuel Church Cemetery Committee, 1949 (Box 37)
    - National American Woman Suffrage Association, undated, 1920 (Box 37)
    - National Congress of Mothers, 1919 (Box 37)
    - Richmond Training School, 1903-1919 (Box 37)
    - Thompson, F.H., 1922 (Box 37)
    - Treasury, Department of, 1919 (Box 37)
    - Virginia, University of--School of Citizenship, 1928 (Box 37)
    - West, J. E. [State Senator], 1921 (Box 37)
  - Subseries C: Alice Dooley/Josephine and Nora Houston, undated, 1915-1953
    - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1921-1953 (Box 37)
    - American Association for Social Security, 1934 (Box 37)
    - American Association of Museums, 1930 (Box 37)
    - American Association of University Women, 1929 (Box 37)
    - American Forestry Association, 1931 (Box 37)
    - Archaeological Institute of America, 1927, 1936 (Box 37)
    - Artists Equity of America, undated (Box 37)
    - Association of Southern Women for the Prevention of Lynching, 1931-1935 (Box 37)
    - Business and Professional Women's Club of Richmond, VA, 1921-1932 (Box 37)
    - Charlottesville Chamber of Commerce, 1931 (Box 37)
    - Chase [William E.] Memorial Fund Committee, 1923 (Box 37)
    - Child Welfare League of America, 1926 (Box 37)
    - Children's Shop, 1929 (Box 37)
    - Citizens' Unemployment Committee, 1930 (Box 37)
    - City Democratic Committee, 1929, 1936 (Box 37)
    - Columbia University, 1929 (Box 37)
    - Commission on Inter-Racial Co-operation, 1922-1940 (Box 37)
    - Cox, James M., 1920 (Box 37)
    - Dietz Press, Inc., undated (Box 37)
    - Dinnen, Matthew Hale, 1923-1924 (Box 37)
    - Drama Guild, 1930 (Box 37)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1925-1932 (Box 37)
    - Girl Scouts of Richmond, undated 1929 (Box 37)
    - Glass, Carter [U.S. Senator], undated (Box 37)
    - Grumbacher, M., 1929 (Box 37)
    - Hampton Alumni Association, 1931 (Box 37)
    - Hinds, Noble and Eldredge, 1914-1928 (Box 37)
    - Home for Needy Confederate Women, 1943 (Box 37)
    - Information Bureau on Women's Work, 1929-1932 (Box 37)
    - Instructive Visiting Nurse Association (IVNA), 1929 (Box 37)
    - International Mercantile Marine Company, 1927 (Box 37)
    - Kappa Alpha Journal, 1930 (Box 38)
    - La Revue Moderne, 1932 (Box 38)
    - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, 1925 (Box 38)
    - Liberal Arts College for Women, 1930 (Box 38)
    - Literary Digest, undated, 1928 (Box 38)
    - Little Theatre League of Richmond, undated, 1920-1927 (Box 38)
    - Lutetia Hotel--Paris, undated (Box 38)
    - Mapp, G. Walter [Senator], 1923 (Box 38)
    - Mapp, G. Walter [Senator] Campaign, 1929 (Box 38)
    - Miller and Rhoads, 1929 (Box 38)
    - Montague, Hill, 1929 (Box 38)
    - Monticello Shop, 1929 (Box 38)
    - Morris Plan Bank of Virginia, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Mountain Mission School, 1931 (Box 38)
    - Mount de Chantal Alumnae Association, 1926 (Box 38)
    - Mullen, Arthur E., 1924 (Box 38)
    - National Child Welfare Association, Inc. 1926 (Box 38)
    - National Consumers League, [Lucy R. Mason] 1934 (Box 38)
    - National Council for Prevention of War, undated, 1932-33 (Box 38)
    - National Education Association, 1923 (Box 38)
    - National Geographic Society, undated, 1924-1930 (Box 38)
    - National Probation Association, 1933 (Box 38)
    - National Save-A-Life League, 1933 (Box 38)
    - National Society of Penal Information, Inc., 1930 (Box 38)
    - Negro Welfare Council, 1931-1933 (Box 38)
    - Old White Art Colony, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Palmer House [Chicago, IL], 1928 (Box 38)
    - Phillips, Mary E., 1927 (Box 38)
    - Pollard, J. Garland [Governor], 1932 (Box 38)
    - Pollard, J. Garland [Governor] Campaign, 1929 (Box 38)
    - Publishers Service Company, 1942 (Box 38)
    - Randolph Macon College, 1928 (Box 38)
    - Railroad YMCA, 1932 (Box 38)
    - Revue du Vraiet du Beau, 1924 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Branch Foreign Policy Association, 1928 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Community Fund, 1926-1937 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Council of Social Agencies, 1925 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Evening Journal, 1916 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Female Institute Alumnae Association, 1932 (Box 38)
    - Richmond News-Leader, 1923 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Public Schools, 1936 (Box 38)
    - Richmond School of Social Work and Public Health [RPI/VCU], 1926 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Tuberculosis Association, 1929-1933 (Box 38)
    - Richmond Workers' Education Committee, 1935 (Box 38)
    - St. Luke's Hospital-McGuire Clinic, 1933 (Box 38)
    - St. Vincent's Hospital, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Save the Children Fund, undated, 1935 (Box 38)
    - Sheltering Arms Hospital, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Shockoe Cemetery, 1931 (Box 38)
    - Social Service Federation--Minutes, undated (Box 38)
    - Southern Women's Educational Alliance, 1930 (Box 38)
    - State Commission on Conservation and Development, 1935 (Box 38)
    - State Planters Bank and Trust Company, 1926-1937 (Box 38)
    - United Daughters of the Confederacy, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Valentine Museum, 1922-1941 (Box 38)
    - Virginia Commission for the Blind, 1930 (Box 38)
    - Virginia Bureau of Labor and Industrial Statistics, 1923 (Box 38)
    - Virginia Department of Labor Industry, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1920 (Box 38)
    - Virginia, University of, 1920-1933 (Box 38)
    - Bureau of University Travel, 1927 (Box 38)
    - West Virginia Mine Workers Union, undated (Box 38)
    - Woman's Auxiliary of the Richmond Academy of Medicine, 1925 (Box 38)
    - Woman's Club of Ashland, undated (Box 38)
    - Woman's Club of Richmond, 1926-1933 (Box 38)
    - Woman's Prohibition League of America, 1918 (Box 38)
    - Worker's Education Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 38)
    - Yorktown Sesquicentennial Association, 1931 (Box 38)
    - Young Women's Christian Association [YWCA], 1920, 1931 (Box 38)